- In the abstract, blackbox is not considered modern planner.

- On Page2, “Our approach is similar in spirit to the idea of using bagged representations within STRIPS(..) but differs in our provision of a fully automated mechanism to identify object multiplicity and our use of constraints to encode dependencies between different parts of a plan.” I believe that “concurrency” of LinGraph is missing, since bagged rep. does not support concurrency?

- On page 23 “since identical propositions will be aggregated in the same node”, we only aggregate them at the first level. Shall we indicate that?

— new additions..
	

